Are you all right?
Keep quiet now
or we'll be in real trouble.
Don't be afraid.
You're one of us.
My name's Stormend.
And what's yours?
Come on, Hei.
Through here.
Come on down.
The humans,
they abandoned this place.
That's Void,
he's charging
his spiritual energy.
Hey, you're back!
Well someone's home early.
Hm?
A kitten?
Meet Skytiger and Bamboo.
What are you doing
bringing a cat back here?
Hmm?
I'm not a cat, I'm a spirit.
Hmm. Mm-hm.
- Ah!
- What's with the ears?
Huh?
This form's not perfect yet.
Aw, aren't you cute?
Skytiger, give the kid
a friendly welcome.
Meat.
Master Infinity, I found him.
I found Stormend.
To our new friend, Hei, cheers.
- Hei?
- Hm?
I can tell you're on edge.
Let me show you something.
Huh?
Hm?
Ah!
Oh?
You're pretty good with kids.
Wanna help make snowflakes?
No.
- Oh?
- Meat.
Mmm!
The meat stole your show.
Ah...
Hei, you know
you can stay with us.
I wha...? Uh, stay?
- That a no?
- Uh...
I'd love to!
From now on, this is your home.
Yeah!
- Booze?
- Hm?
Not for him.
Come.
What do you think?
- Go on.
- Ah?
This room's all yours.
I'll leave you to it,
get some sleep.
Hei?
Infinity, you're a human.
Why are you helping the Guild?
Not here to explain myself.
I'm taking you back.
Run!
Ah!
Hei, come back here!
- Get moving!
- What?
Go!
Now!
Where is this?
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
We lost Hei
and we lost the portal.
How could one human
send us packing?
It's Infinity,
their best Enforcer.
He's no ordinary human.
So we're gonna let him take Hei?
Of course not.
Can you track him?
Mm-hm,
got a mark on Hei already.
That's a start.
Infinity's gonna take him
to the Guild.
We can stop him.
We're no match for him.
Just find him.
I'll take care of Infinity.
You mean...?
I'm tired of waiting.
I see.
Leave finding Hei to us.
Thanks, I'm counting on you.
Where are we anyway?
I set this escape route
up last time
just in case
we got ambushed again.
My seeds can detect anything
within a 500-yard radius.
I'll know
when they leave the island.
How do you know where
they're going to leave from?
Well to be honest, I don't.
We'll have to spread these
along the coastline.
Got it.
Tiger, we're gonna need
some help.
Get your friends.
Stormend!
Stormend, Bamboo, Skytiger!
Stormend, Bamboo, Stormend!
So you don't know
how to leave either?
Your friends ran.
I'm taking you to the Guild.
Be good, you hear me?
Stormend?
You saved me
the trouble of looking for you.
We're about to set off.
Hm?
Behave yourself.
Just sit and wait.
Do you... hear me?
From now on,
this is your home.
- Mr. Min.
- Huh? Stormend.
It's been so long.
You looking to share some tea?
I have a favor to ask.
If the Guild permits it,
I'm happy to help.
What'd you need?
Stormend, there is no shame
in moving on.
Sometimes we must let go.
I know.
Now, may I borrow something,
Mr. Min?
Do you prefer being tied up?
And the coconuts?
Master!
Good morning, Master.
- Maomao.
- Yes?
- Help me up please.
- Sure.
You broke my purple clay teapot.
My apologies, Master.
Hm?
What awful weather.
Hm.
A dragon.
Well, that's rare.
Is this...
The Zone?
What's your name?
It's Hei.
Hei, huh?
Try to use your power again.
What power?
Wha... ah!
- Get in.
- Uh!
Just try and make me!
Mm? Hm?
Whoa, what is this place?
This is my Spiritual Space.
What?
Every living thing
has a Spiritual Space
to call their own,
a place to sow our spirit.
These places are the source
of all life and power.
Do I have a Spiritual Space too?
Of course.
And does it have a house in it?
No, yours is empty.
This is my childhood home.
I've been keeping it here.
Got any food in there?
No.
Give me your hand.
Mm? What for?
Hm?
Maybe I was wrong.
What the heck is
this crazy place? Huh?
- Hei.
- Huh?
You want to learn
how to control metal?
Huh?
I checked out your magic system.
You're Metal-type,
just like me.
But why teach me?
Call it payback.
Huh?
Because you're gifted.
What?
Let's start by understanding
the properties of metal.
It's salty.
That might just be my sweat.
I don't want your training!
It's up to you.
I won't force you.
It couldn't hurt
to try, right?
Once I've mastered the power,
I can use it to escape.
Forcing it won't work.
Then what should I do?
Come here.
Hm.
Yeah!
He really is gifted.
Excuse me.
We're closed for the night.
Are you Brush Tiger?
And you are?
Well, young man, if there's
anything that interests you
in my humble shop,
please do let me know.
Call them off.
Come on out or
I'll tear this place down.
So that's your true form?
What do you want?
Your name's Infinity, right?
Yes.
I thought you could fly.
Why don't we just fly back?
I can't fly that far.
Useless.
Why were you chasing Stormend?
Hey, you listening?
Hm.
Once we've landed,
can you let me go?
Sure.
Hm? Really?
Do you mean it?
Say something!
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
Pipe down.
Found him!
Here's the mainland,
here's the island and here's us.
They deviated
about a thousand miles south.
He has no sense of direction.
The fairy fish can't keep up.
They'll lose them before long.
What Guild is nearest
to their landing?
Longyou.
Then that's where we're going.
But that's Guild turf.
So we stop them
before they arrive.
Mm.
Longyou.
We made it.
Huh?
- Land ho!
- Hm?
Dry land at last!
- Woo-hoo!
- Hey!
Hm?
What are you doing here?
Hello. What is this place?
Uh, Xiaoxiang Island.
Or rather which province?
Mm.
You're stowaways, ain't you?
No, just lost.
And you're just wandered
into another province?
Let me explain.
Explain, my foot!
Hey, call the cops.
Hm?
I am a stowaway.
So please,
tell me which province is this?
Fulan province.
Well, I'll see you around.
- Let me buy you a meal.
- Hm?
I'll take this one and that one.
Oh, this too, this one,
one of those, this one,
and definitely this!
Our food's all made
with local ingredients
but we specialize in seafood.
Can I interest you in...
Nope.
Okay.
If there's
one thing that the humans
are good at, it's cooking!
We accept mobile pay.
This pendant's
my greatest treasure.
It should be more than enough
to pay for this meal.
Mm?
Stop those dine and dashers!
Dine and dash?
I could have done that
when I was alone and homeless.
That was an accident.
Anyway, later.
Where are you going?
To find Stormend.
Hey, come with me.
- Huh?
- To the Guild.
Get these off of me!
You told me you were gonna
let me go, dang it!
I lied.
I'm sorry.
I can't let you go.
All you want
is a place to stay, right?
Not if I gotta stay
with you humans!
Mm.
It's called the Spirit Guild
because it was formed
by your kind.
But aren't you a human?
Right now
I'm more spirit than human.
It's not like I live there.
I'm just an Enforcer.
What's an Enforcer?
Like a law Enforcer.
Huh?
I'm like a helper
to the spirits.
Are there other humans
in the Guild?
- Some.
- I'm not going.
You can either come along
with me nicely
- or I can hogtie you.
- Hm!
You're a jerk!
Let me go!
I'll punish you
if you try to run again.
I won't so just put me down!
You need to hide your tail too.
Let me go!
Your two-hour
punishment begins now.
Let me go!
Hm? Ah?
Huh?
Ah.
Hm!
Why are you always so mad at me?
'Cause you're a bad guy.
So is Stormend.
No, he isn't!
You didn't know him
for that long.
He gave me food
and he gave me a home.
- I gave you food too.
- Uh...
Hm.
It's not the food's fault.
What was this bird?
Don't think the bird's
the problem.
Why don't you fly over?
Flying without
permission is forbidden.
Lame.
Ah!
- No more drain pipes.
- Hm?
Oh.
Mm?
Mm-mm!
You want revenge on humanity?
Of course.
So what, you'll kill them all?
Not sure yet.
I just want to go
back to the forest.
Hm.
Quit it!
- They're done.
- Hm?
These should be good.
I guess not.
How do we look?
Pretty good.
They're not here yet.
Then let's start our
search by fanning out from here.
Let no one see you
and use extra caution
near the landing point.
What about Stormend?
We hold them
until Stormend arrives.
Have you heard of The Zone?
No.
It's another power you possess.
The Zone?
Is it cool?
It's like my Devour,
a Space-type power,
from the idiosyncrasies
of your Spiritual Space.
My Spiritual Space, huh?
Question, can't we just sleep
in that little cabin
you have in yours?
I can, you can't.
Thanks a lot.
Entering a Spiritual Space
can't be taken lightly.
Why?
The owner of a space
is essentially it's God,
go in rashly,
and they'll trample you.
Already feels like
you're trampling me out here.
Hardly.
Remember when we were in there?
How I teleported and moved you?
Mm.
You can't out here?
Right.
I only have those powers
in my Spiritual Space.
I could basically
turn you into a puppet in there.
Mm.
Just forget it.
Now you don't wanna go in?
Hm!
All right.
- That's enough.
- Huh?
The boy was trying to sleep.
Infinity, I missed you so much.
Hey! What's going on?
Relax, they're friends.
Did you take on an apprentice?
I'm not his apprentice.
No.
Hm...
Liar, he's a Metal and
Space hybrid like you.
Hm? Are you spirits?
Mm-hm.
They're all Enforcers
for the Guild.
Even spirits run errands
for 'em.
Huh? What do you mean, errands?
Enforcer is a sacred title!
He's not wrong.
- What?
Anyway, I'm going to bed.
Weren't you sent
to capture Stormend?
Yeah, he got away.
Then why haven't you
told the Guild?
You're dragging your feet.
What are you after?
I wanted to show him around.
Hm, I can see
why you're tempted,
it's rare to find
such a perfect type match.
Been a century
since your last apprentice.
Don't overthink it.
I just don't
want him to go astray.
You out on a mission?
Yes, but Flow
sensed your presence
and insisted we pay you a visit.
She dragged us
all the way up here
in the vain hope that she...
You have something
you want to say, old man?
I wouldn't dare, sweetie.
Hm!
Oh, by the way, do you plan
on taking Hei to the Guild?
Mm-hm.
I'll be long gone by the time
he even gets to the place.
Hm?
It seems we have a split vote.
I bet he hasn't told you
a thing about the Guild.
Don't mind that sad sack.
The Guild's a spectacular place.
They offer guidance
for little spirits, like you,
but they also help us old fogies
adapt to the modern world.
Then why are they after
Stormend?
Stormend.
I don't bear him any ill will.
It's his hatred of humanity.
He can't keep himself
from crossing the line.
We have attempted to talk to him
time and time again,
but he just keeps
shutting us out.
But the humans are evil.
Humans are like spirits.
They're not all bad or good.
And sometimes it's hard
to distinguish the two,
complex as we are.
The human-spirit relationship
has finally reached
a delicate balance,
a balance
we have to work to protect.
Why do we have to
get along with humans?
Do you actually like them?
Sure do!
Not really.
Many spirits prefer to stay
as far from human society
as they can,
but even living in their cities,
doesn't mean
we have to love them.
Look at those two,
they even hate Infinity.
I just mad I haven't
kicked his ass yet.
- You said it!
- You two are so shameless.
Hey cat, you want to come hang
with some real spirits?
Nah, you guys are wimps.
I don't much like
being around humans myself.
I use to have a cave house.
There was nothing like it.
Then humans turned it into
a tourist attraction
about 10 years ago.
Can't go home without a ticket.
It was deep in the wilderness.
I lived there
for hundreds of years.
Finding a place
out of humanity's reach
nowadays is impossible.
I honestly love humans.
- Uh.
- They're so creative.
It's like they invent
new gadgets every day.
Like this, it's a sound
transmission device.
And take a look,
it does so much more than that.
A lot of spirits at the Guild
are obsessed with them.
Hm?
Humans are so interesting.
And none more than our Infinity.
You can say that again.
Listen Hei, Infinity's done
so much for us spirits.
Please don't
hold anything against him.
Go check out the Guild.
If you don't like it
no one will
stop you from leaving
because we've got your back.
Okay, raise your cups,
everyone.
Oh, one sec.
You too, Infinity.
Hm.
You guys too, get over here.
Well, I won't turn down a drink.
Too true!
Cheers!
We should probably
be on our way.
Bye, Hei.
I'll see you again at the Guild.
Hold on.
I need cash.
Money is the best.
Our riches have changed you.
...ride that?
We could even buy our own.
Hey gorgeous!
Why didn't we get one of those?
I can't drive.
You moron.
Listen up in there!
We've got you surrounded!
Hm?
You have to surrender now!
You wanna bet?
Hm?
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
I, uh, surrender?
- You full?
- Mm-hm.
You said I'm a Space type
so why can't I use those powers?
Give it time.
You think I can master Devour
like you?
You only get one Space power.
So no.
Then is The Zone more powerful
than your Devour?
Depends on who's using them.
That's a yes.
You still have a lot to learn.
You're jealous.
Mind your manners.
You're a human,
why are you so powerful?
Wanna be my apprentice?
Mm. Oh.
Mm?
Ah! Mm.
Hei?
If you end up hating the Guild,
I'll let you go.
I've heard that one before.
You really are talented and
you will grow up to be strong.
But if you do choose to leave,
I hope you use
your powers for good.
I never do anything bad.
Can you tell the difference?
Of course.
Yeah, I believe you.
Stormend isn't a bad person.
Neither are you.
But you're not great either.
Hm?
Now this is a fine mess.
You'd never seen him before?
Mm-mm.
Oh, I got it.
Hold this and think of his face.
- Hm?
- Okay, let me see.
Huh?
Was this him?
Yeah, a Wood-type spirit.
It was Stormend.
Stormend?
He's never raised a hand
against a spirit before.
He even stole my power.
What? Does he have that ability?
Hm,
not to my knowledge.
An impostor maybe.
Or he's hidden this from us.
Stealing powers
is strictly forbidden.
But are we
jumping to conclusions?
We'll know the truth
soon enough.
Flow, we're the fastest,
let's go on ahead.
Right.
Mr. Brush Tiger,
allow Bless to escort you
to the Spirit Guild.
Okay.
Let's go.
How much farther?
We'll see it
once we're through the tunnel.
Come on out.
Is this it?
We're out of gas.
We'll take the subway.
The what?
It's like a really long car.
Why, you scared?
No.
Hop on.
Only 'cause I hate
walking on the street.
Sure.
So this is definitely
a human city, right?
Correct.
Most of the Guild branches
are in cities.
This city is called Longyou.
It's home to 10 million people
and 500 spirits.
That many?
Plenty of spirits love cities
and the variety of lifestyles
they provide.
They can live in
whatever form they want
provided they follow
one key rule,
keep a low profile.
Master Infinity!
I sensed you from miles away.
What are you up to?
Flower delivery.
Hm?
Adorable!
Where did you adopt him?
- I'm not a pet, I'm a hostage.
- Hm?
Ah, so you're one of us.
My bad, didn't realize,
no hard feelings.
You're an Enforcer too?
Hm?
No, nothing like that.
I'm just a junior flower spirit.
Master Infinity adopted me too.
Are you heading to the Guild?
Yes, I'm taking Hei there.
It'll be nice
to have you around for a while.
Oh, right, my deliveries.
I better go Master Infinity.
I'll see you at the Guild, Hei!
Oh yeah,
and welcome to the big city.
You're gonna love it here.
Bye-bye!
Are there are a lot of
spirits in human cities?
Tons.
Shall we?
We're almost there.
Uh, cats aren't allowed
on the subway.
Oh.
What's this?
Uh!
Are we really
under the ground right now?
We got him.
Oh?
There really is a car
and it's so long.
Wrong way.
It's there.
That one goes
in a different direction.
Come get in line,
don't wander off.
Don't hurt them.
They're being controlled.
But for what? Hm?
What's happening?
Teleportation!
Hm?
Night-night.
He knows where we are.
My bad,
could only warp him so far.
They'll stop the train
if we make a scene.
I'll control the engineer.
You do your thing.
Sure, Roger that.
Hm?
Hey, mister.
That kid can't be comfy
like that.
Sorry, sir, but are you
that boy's guardian?
Hey, is that your kid
or not?
Sir, please answer
the question.
Hey, say something.
Probably human traffickers.
What kind of person
would treat his own son
- like that?
- Put the kid down.
- That can't be his Dad.
- Put him down already.
What'd you do?
That'll stop him.
Stop him.
Hei.
Mm!
Papa, Papa, Papa,
wake up, wake up!
Is he okay?
- Look after the passengers.
- Huh?
He's stubborn.
- Nicely done.
- Hm?
We'll work on your strength.
Save yourself the public...
embarrassment.
Who are these people?
Hm?
Spirits.
What about that kid?
- He's not gonna eat us, is he?
- Sh!
Are you hurt?
Not even a scratch.
Then let's go.
- Hey, hero boy!
- Hm?
Thank you.
No prob.
You are quite the charmer.
Hm.
Guild members
are already on their way.
Let's wait up here.
Why were they trying
to kidnap me?
No idea.
We'll ask when they wake up.
Why are we on the roof?
The fewer people who see us
the easier it'll be
for the Guild.
If the driver doesn't wake up
though,
I might need to
stop the train myself.
You told me
to keep those humans safe.
And you did quite well.
Hm?
Hei, I'm taking you home.
Stormend!
Hei, he's with those guys.
Hm?
Keep Hei safe.
Stop fighting!
- You've improved.
- Damn right!
Mr. Min's Sonic Wave!
Damn it.
Hei, I'll come find you!
- Infinity.
- Go help them.
- Was it Stormend?
- Mm-hm.
We recently discovered
that he's capable of
stealing powers.
He is?
I hadn't heard of this.
He has kept it a secret
all this time.
Then he only wanted Hei
for his power.
Is that the little spirit
Mr. Turtledove told me about?
Correct.
Hei has The Zone.
- Are you certain of that?
- Yes.
Then Hei is in danger.
If that power
is taken away from him...
I never saw him as a threat.
That was a mistake.
We need to find him fast.
I've arranged for
Longyou's borders to be closed.
He won't escape.
Good, let me know
what you turn up.
You're not taking command?
We have you, Hei only has me.
Guild Master,
we've attended to the crash.
No fatalities.
Erase their memories.
Let the humans do the rest.
Send all of our Sentients
after Stormend
and evacuate all civilians
from the city.
Mobilize everyone,
we'll need backup from HQ.
That's serious?
It'll cause a panic.
I'll ask the mayor to cooperate.
We need to prepare
for the worst.
The Zone is something
even the High Lord can't dispel.
- We can't take it lightly.
- Got it.
You said that the boy's powers
could be taken away.
What would happen to him?
A normal power
would be lost temporarily,
restored with practice.
But a Space-type power
draws on one's Spiritual Space
any spirit robbed of that...
dies.
So it begins.
You're not hurt, are you?
Not one bit.
Did you miss me at all?
Mm-hm.
Stormend?
- Hm?
- Are you okay?
I'm good.
Mm, uh...
Do you hate the spirits
of the Guild?
What'd they say to you?
They said the Guild is a home
to all spirits
and asked me to stay.
Stay here?
Of course,
this is my hometown, after all.
Huh?
This cold,
concrete city used to be
a place of extraordinary power.
Lots of spirits were born here
and their presence made
the forest
grow lush and strong.
It was a paradise.
And then came humans.
They cut down trees to build
houses and feed their fires.
In time, they became
part of the forest.
I didn't hate them then.
They were fun
in their own way.
Humans are frail
and emotional.
They revered and respected us.
At least they did
in the good old days.
But then
their evolution accelerated.
A lot of our fellow spirits
chose to leave
but if anyone
was getting forced out
I thought it should be them.
That's when the Guild
stepped in.
They disagreed with our values.
We were defeated,
we had to leave our home.
Why have we been reduced
to this?
If it keeps going this way,
humans will dominate the spirits
and the Guild maintains
this unfair balance.
But we can fix it together.
You might not have realized,
but your power, The Zone,
can expand your Spiritual Space.
Wherever you use it
becomes your domain.
And in that domain,
you're the God.
I... haven't mastered it.
Well, I'll help you.
We'll drive out all the humans
and make this our home.
Oh.
Is this why
you were so nice to me?
Mm?
Please Hei, don't forget,
the humans drove us out first.
Uh, I won't forget,
but even so this isn't right.
You still don't get it.
All they do is take and destroy.
Even the ones you trust.
Stormend, if you hate humans
that much
we can live somewhere
far away from them.
Let's leave this place together
and find another home
like the island.
That was a nice place too,
wasn't it?
We'll let them have the city
and start a new life
somewhere else.
Stormend, don't do this!
Stormend, let me talk to him,
please!
- I don't mind moving.
- Stormend!
- But it won't be long...
- Come on! Wait!
...till there's nowhere left
for us.
Please Hei, forgive me.
I have to take your power.
Stormend.
Stormend, stop! Stormend!
Don't do this, I'm begging you,
Stormend!
The Zone, at last.
We got word from HQ,
they've given Stormend's power
the name Snatch.
It's the most aggressive power
of its kind.
It can rob a spirit of
their chi and power alike.
He's taken Sonic Wave,
Magical Brush and Time Bomb
to use against you.
These stolen powers
won't last forever
but if his real target
is The Zone,
then once
that's called into being,
there can be no dispelling it.
So it is with
all Space-type powers.
That bastard.
Master Infinity.
- Huh?
- I've detected
Stormend's spiritual wave.
The Sentients must've
noticed the power I used.
We need to split up.
Once you've seen The Zone
come into being, come find us.
Got it.
Go.
Void.
Hei, Hei.
It's me, it's me, Hei.
It's Infinity, I'm here.
Will he be okay?
His Spiritual Spaces is
fading rapidly.
I'll take him to the High Lord.
If the High Lord could help
we wouldn't need to use
the Fire Rock.
How do I save him?
Take back
Hei's stolen Spiritual Space.
Give me Stormend's
possible locations.
I'm leaving Hei to you.
Don't worry.
Scratch location one, it's Void.
Requesting backup.
He's not at location seven.
Just Brush Tiger's
paint monster.
They've put Stormend's scent
on all of them.
Location three empty,
where's the next one?
Infinity!
Give Hei's Spiritual Space back.
It's already been stabilized.
The process can't be reversed.
You're a step behind.
Why did you take that step?
How can you claim
you're helping spirit-kind
if you're killing Hei to do it?
I... owe you nothing.
Listen...
give up before it's too late.
I still haven't figured out
how a human could get so strong.
Still, I'm not gonna surrender
to one.
Not when I owe my brothers
so much.
Stormend!
Infinity.
Everybody run!
Move out and cut all signal,
commence cleanup.
On it.
All Enforcers be advised,
all Enforcers be advised,
The Zone is being created
in the center of downtown.
Move to a surrounding area
and prioritize evacuation.
Mommy...
...with a special report.
Strange shadows all over
Longyou...
All the cars are stopped.
Move it!
No, we're not gonna make it.
Biggie, do it, you got it.
Master, how do we contain
a mess this large?
One problem at a time.
Can't open the door.
- Out of the car!
- Tiger!
Hm! Huh?
Oh come on!
Huh?
Sending you the location
of every remaining civilian.
Received.
Infinity, you followed me in?
You well know the danger of
entering someone else's space.
I do,
but I can't let you do this!
This space is mine.
And that means you're nothing.
...reporting live
from Longyou City,
where a massive, shadowy orb
of sorts
seems to be consuming
the downtown district
and growing larger.
You guys serious?
These are the chumps
giving you trouble?
- Master Nezha.
- Guild Master.
Infinity's gone into The Zone.
That doesn't sound like him.
Why'd he do that?
So reckless, he doesn't stand
a chance on his own in there
so I'm going in
to help clean all this up.
Hmm, did anyone mention
that the space was closed?
Hm?
What's going on?
Oh, you wanna play?
Uh? What the heck?
Space-type powers
are such a pain in the ass!
So did HQ send anyone else or?
It's nothing
I can't take care of.
Uh, good luck then.
Lousy stupid Space-type powers.
How'd it go?
Most civilians are safe.
What about Hei?
Still unconscious.
The expansion of The Zone
has slowed,
Infinity must've
located Stormend.
We can only hope Hei
will hold out until he returns.
Hei, you know
you can stay with us.
I wha...?
From now on this is your home.
Yeah!
Stormend, don't do this!
I don't mind moving,
but it won't be long till
there's nowhere left for us.
Stormend.
I have to take your power.
Hm?
Does this mean that I'm dead?
Huh?
Stormend!
Infinity?
Infinity, stop fighting it.
You know you can't win
in my space.
You hurt other spirits.
Disgraced your people,
and for what, this empty city?
I wouldn't say empty.
This city is colossal.
There are still plenty of humans
trapped in here.
What do you think?
Will the Guild
want to trade hostages?
Don't move!
You know, there's
no going back for me now.
Not after all I've done.
If Hei had never met you,
we'd be creating The Zone
together right now,
building a home for spirit-kind.
Reclaiming this land
would've made him happy too.
But what a shame,
that time has passed.
What the...?
Hei!
Who says I'd be happy?
This is some kind of trick!
Huh?
You all right?
I don't know.
It felt like I was taking a nap
and in my dream I heard
you getting your butt kicked.
In order for us
to get out of here,
we gotta beat Stormend,
and Hei, I can't do it alone.
Huh?
But I don't even know
how I did that earlier.
- I can't even...
- You can.
This is your Spiritual Space.
In here, all things big or small
are under your control.
Besides, I'm with you.
Mm-hm.
- Oh, and sorry.
- Oh?
Go.
How dare you!
Hei!
Just remember,
this is your Spiritual Space.
This space is mine!
- Die!
- Hei!
Uh Hei, did you do this?
Uh...
Whoa.
This can't be.
This can't be happening!
I'll kill...
Now's the time.
Tear down the space.
Hei, with The Zone you are God,
do you want to throw that away?
If you tear it down,
you can never get that back.
Neither can you.
Hei!
Don't do it!
Hei, stop.
Don't take this... from me.
Hm?
It's done.
Infinity.
Search for the ones
who are trapped inside.
Got it.
We have much work ahead of us.
Our long-maintained balance
is broken.
Tearing down trust is easier
than building it back up.
Stormend.
Humans and spirits have to find
a way to coexist.
There's no point
in fighting each other.
Coexist, hm,
you want us to assimilate?
You still think you're right,
after all that.
Well I encourage you
to think on it
while you're in Guild custody.
I've thought enough.
This time...
I'm not leaving my home.
Hm.
Hei, I'm sorry.
What's the point?
We're just gonna
cut the thing down.
Perhaps they will turn it into
a park and charge admission.
I think we all have
a ways to go.
Was he... was Stormend bad?
That's a question you'll have to
answer for yourself.
Infinity!
Huh? Hei!
Double Spiritual Spaces.
That is how he came back.
A person with
two spaces is rare messages.
Master Mysteria is the only
other one I know of.
Hm, it is historically
a rare occurrence.
But a Double-space-type
is all the more so.
Truly a shame.
Infinity, where are Bamboo
and Void?
In custody.
Well, what happens next?
They'll be locked up
for a long while.
Hm?
What's up?
You want an autograph?
You're a guy, right?
Yep.
Your hair's a little too cute.
I'd change it
if it weren't so iconic.
What do you mean?
Hm, who are you?
- See?
- Who are you though?
- I'm kind of a big deal.
- Oh.
- We're finally here.
- Hm?
Master Infinity,
Master Infinity!
Hey, Guild Master!
Hm?
Come on,
I'll show you around the place.
- Huh?
- Hm?
Hei?
I think it's time
we said goodbye.
Mm-hm.
What do you mean?
Aren't you gonna stay?
Can't, I'm not very popular
around here.
Mostly because
he's too powerful.
Some of the locals feel
a bit uneasy when he's around.
You're going to love it here.
I'll come check on you
when I can.
Master!
Ohh.
Let...
Let me come with you, Infinity!
Of course.
So they're just stopping by?
Could have told us that.
Oh, what do you know?
Yes, sir.
- Hm?
- Totally right.
I'm coming with you too, Master!
You sure you want
to wander the world?
I thought you wanted
to find a home.
Mm-mm.
I just wanna be with you.
Yeah,
me too.